Guide to the Stanford University, Faculty Senate, Records SC0193
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Academic Council records, 1966-1975; Series 1
  - 4th Senate, 10/26/1971 - 05/28/1972 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Committee on Tresidder Union (C-TU) minutes; Trustees.
  - 4th Senate, 09/29/1971 - 01/26/1972 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 4th Senate, 02/02/1972 - 05/31/1972 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - 4th Senate, 03/01/1972 - 06/20/1972 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Committee on Undergraduate Studies (C-US) meetings, press releases, minutes.
  - 4th Senate, 11/01/1971 - 05/25/1972 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Committee on Undergraduate Studies /Advising(C-US-A) minutes.
  - 4th Senate (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Committee on Undergraduate Studies /Entering Students(C-US-ES) minutes; C-US-Student innovation/SCIRE evaluations.
  - 4th Senate, 11/01/1971 - 02/10/1972 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Special Joint Agency: Stanford Workshops on Political and Social Issues (SJA-SWOPSI) minutes.
  - 4th Senate (Box 24, Folder 8)
    Special Joint Agency: Committee on Undergraduate Studies - Urban Studies (SJA-PUS); University budget (AC-UEAP); University governance; University Press (P-UP); Vietnam War/press releases.
  - 4th Senate (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Committee on Committees evaluation.
  - 4th Senate (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Committee on Committees reports.
  - 4th Senate (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Committee on Committees worksheets (1).
  - 4th Senate (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Committee on Committees worksheets (2).
  - 4th Senate, 11/19/1971 - 06/02/1972 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Committee on Computation Facilities (C-CF) minutes.
  - 4th Senate (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Degrees.
  - 4th Senate, 10/04/1971 - 05/30/1972 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Committee on the Education and Employment of Women in the University (C-EEWU) minutes.
  - 4th Senate, 05/24/1971 - 12/22/1971 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Steering Committee (StC) minutes & meeting calls.
  - 4th Senate, 01/12/1972 - 06/01/1972 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - 4th Senate, 06/02/1971 - 07/26/1971 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Committee on Committees (CoC) minutes & meeting calls.
  - 4th Senate, 09/14/1971 - 12/09/1971 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - 4th Senate, 01/04/1972 - 05/16/1972 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 4th Senate, 10/01/1971 - 01/18/1972 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement (C-AAA) minutes.
  - 4th Senate, 02/01/1972 - 05/23/1972 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - 4th Senate (Box 26, Folder 6)
    Academic calendar; Academic Planning (A-PO); Advisory Board.
  - 4th Senate (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Affirmative Action; Alumni Relations; Articles of Organization of the Faculty; Athletics, Physical Education & Recreation (C-APER).
  - 4th Senate (Box 26, Folder 8)
    Business & finance; cable television (C-CaTV); Campaign for Stanford; campus disruption.
  - 5th Senate, 05/18/1972 - 06/14/1973 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - 5th Senate, 05/18/1972 - 10/26/1972 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - 5th Senate, 11/09/1972 - 02/22/1973 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 5th Senate, 03/08/1973 - 06/14/1973 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 5th Senate, 12/19/1972 - 06/15/1973 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Senate Advisory Board.
  - 5th Senate (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Affirmative action.
  - 5th Senate (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Alumni relations; Articles of Organization; ASSU Constitution.
  - 5th Senate, 10/25/1972 - 06/06/1973 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    Committee on Athletics, Physical Education, and Recreation (C-APER) minutes (includes C-APER subcommittee on recreational programs & facilities minutes - 11/17/1972 - 02/23/1973).
  - 5th Senate (Box 27, Folder 9)
    Business & finance; Campaign for Stanford.
  - 5th Senate, 02/15/1973 - 06/15/1973 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Committee on Foreign Study Programs (C-FSP) minutes & reports (includes subcommittee - Commission for the Review of Overseas Campuses, C-ROSC).
  - 5th Senate, 11/15/1972 - 05/21/1973 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Committee on Foreign Study Programs (C-FSP) subcommittees on Austria, Britain, France, Germany, Italy, minutes.
  - 5th Senate, 09/27/1972 - 08/08/1973 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Committee on Graduate Studies (C-GS) minutes.
  - 5th Senate (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Committee on Graduate Studies - Graduate Special Programs (C-GS-GSP); Graduate Education Study (SGES).
  - 5th Senate (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Health (P-HS).
  - Academic Secretary's Documents (Box 28, Folder 6)
    Faculty self-discipline.
  - Academic Secretary's Documents, 11/03/1972 - 03/02/1973 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    Committee on Faculty & Staff Affairs (C-FSA) minutes (includes C-FSA/Committee on the Professoriate at Stanford).
  - Academic Secretary's Documents, 02/08/1973 - 05/24/1973 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Academic Secretary's Documents, 02/08/1973 - 05/24/1973 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    Foreign policy; Foreign Study Programs (C-FSP) includes Commission for the Review of Overseas Campuses (C-ROSC).
  - 5th Senate, 05/22/1972 - 11/21/1972 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - 5th Senate, 12/06/1972 - 03/07/1973 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - 5th Senate, 03/14/1973 - 06/06/1973 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - 5th Senate, 06/06/1972 - 11/02/1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - 5th Senate, 12/07/1972 - 05/24/1973 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - 5th Senate (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Committee on Committees (CoC) evaluations of University committees performance.
  - 5th Senate (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Committee on Committees (CoC) reports & worksheets.
  - 5th Senate, 11/16/1972 - 08/16/1973 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - 5th Senate (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - 5th Senate, 06/07/1971? - 06/04/1973 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Committee on the Education and Employment of Women at the University (C-EEWU) minutes.
  - 5th Senate (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Faculty handbook.
  - Academic Secretary's Office, Spring 1973 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    Committee worksheets.
  - Academic Secretary's Office, 26999 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    Committee rosters.
  - Academic Secretary's Office, 26816 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    Master lists: faculty & students A - Z.
  - Academic Secretary's Office, 1972 - 1973 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Academic Secretary's Office, 1971 - 1972 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Academic Secretary's Office, 1970 - 1971 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Academic Secretary's Office, 1969 - 1970 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Academic Secretary's Office, 1970 - 1974 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    Roster worksheets; log of minutes.
  - 5th Senate, 10/11/1972 - 05/15/1973 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Committee on Academic Appraisal & Achievement (C-AAA) minutes.
  - 5th Senate (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Committee on Academic Appraisal & Achievement Evaluation of Teaching (C-AAA-ET).
  - 5th Senate (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Academic calendar/religious holidays; academic freedom.
  - Academic Secretary's Office, 09/27/1972 - 12/18/1972 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Advisory Board memos & drafts.
  - Academic Secretary's Office (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Information officer & press representation; Investment Responsibility (C-IR); Judicial (CJP).
  - 5th Senate, 10/30/1972 - 07/12/1973 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    Committee on Land & Building Development minutes (includes subcommittee on faculty & staff housing minutes).
  - 5th Senate (Box 31, Folder 7)
    Libraries (C-LIB & ULC).
  - Academic Secretary's Documents (Box 31, Folder 8)
    Meeting schedules; Minority Affairs.
  - Academic Secretary's Documents (Box 31, Folder 9)
    Placement service & recruitment; privacy of information (C-PPI).
  - Academic Secretary's Office (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Academic Secretary's Office, 26481 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Trustees manual.
  - 5th Senate, 26604 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Committee on Undergraduate Admissions & Financial Aids (C-UAFA) report (includes miscellaneous press releases 06/08/1972 - 11/17/1972).
  - 5th Senate, 01/29/1973 - 05/29/1973 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Committee on Undergraduate Admissions & Financial Aids (C-UAFA) minutes.
  - 5th Senate, 09/27/1972 - 07/03/1973 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - 5th Senate, 10/03/1972 - 05/24/1973 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Committee on Public Events (C-PEV) minutes (includes subcommittee on University lectures); Radiological Hazards (P-RHC); relations with student government.
  - 5th Senate, 10/25/1972 - 05/29/1973 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Committee on Research (C-RES) minutes & reports.
  - 5th Senate, 10/25/1972 - 05/29/1973 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - 5th Senate (Box 32, Folder 9)
    ROTC.
  - 5th Senate (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Search committees; Senate attendance.
  - 5th Senate (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Senate election.
  - 5th Senate (Box 33, Folder 2)
    Senate guests.
  - 5th Senate (Box 33, Folder 3)
    Senate rosters.
  - 5th Senate (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - 5th Senate, 11/13/1972 - 06/01/1973 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Services to Students (C-SSt) minutes.
  - 5th Senate (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Stanford police; Steering Committee election; Steering Committee procedures; Student Conduct (SCLC); Tresidder Union (C-TU).
  - Academic Secretary's Office, 12/04/1972 - 02/12/1973 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Committee on Undergraduate Studies (C-US) meetings, memos, reports.
  - Academic Secretary's Office, 02/14/1973 - 11/26/1973 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Academic Secretary's Office (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Committee on Undergraduate Studies (C-US): credit review / entering students / student innovation / SWOPSI / Urban Studies.
  - Academic Secretary's Office, 1973 - 1974 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    University budget (AC-UBAP) report and operating guidelines.
  - Academic Secretary's Office (Box 34, Folder 2)
    University governance; University Press (P-UP).
  - 6th Senate, 05/10/1973 - 06/13/1974 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Senate reports (includes V.1, #7 of "Live Oak" dated 11/08/1974).
  - 6th Senate, 05/10/1973 - 01/24/1974 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - 6th Senate, 02/07/1974 - 06/13/1974 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - 6th Senate, 05/13/1973 - 11/21/1973 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - 6th Senate, 12/05/1973 - 03/27/1974 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - 6th Senate, 04/04/1974 - 06/06/1974 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - 6th Senate, 06/06/1973 - 09/17/1973 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - 6th Senate, 10/04/1973 - 06/06/1974 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - 6th Senate (Box 35, Folder 3)
    Senate Charter; Senate elections; Senate guests.
  - 6th Senate (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Senate roster; Senate rules.
  - 6th Senate, 01/10/1974 - 05/22/1974 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    Committee on Services to Students (C-SSt) minutes; Stanford police.
  - 6th Senate (Box 35, Folder 6)
    Steering Committee (StC) elections; StC procedures.
  - 6th Senate (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - 6th Senate (Box 35, Folder 8)
    Tresidder Union; Trustees.
  - 6th Senate, 10/16/1973 - 05/21/1974 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - 6th Senate, 10/03/1973 - 12/05/1973 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - 6th Senate, 01/16/1974 - 06/05/1974 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - 6th Senate (Box 36, Folder 3)
    University budget (AC-UBAP).
  - 6th Senate (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - 6th Senate (Box 36, Folder 5)
    Academic freedom: memos, meetings, and reports of the Floor Management Committee for the Statement on Academic Freedom (FMC-SAF), Part 1.
  - 6th Senate (Box 36, Folder 6)
    Academic freedom: memos, meetings, and reports of the Floor Management Committee for the Statement on Academic Freedom (FMC-SAF), Part 2.
  - 6th Senate (Box 36, Folder 7)
    Advisory Board; affirmative action.
  - 6th Senate, 11/19/1973 - 04/16/1974 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    Articles of Organization; ASSU Constitution; ASSU Professor; Athletics/PE (C-APER) minutes.
  - 6th Senate (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - 6th Senate (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - 6th Senate, 10/02/1973 - 04/09/1974 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - 6th Senate, 10/18/1973 - 06/11/1974 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    Subcommittees of the C-AAA minutes: Academic Standing, Petition & Exceptions (C-AAA-ASPE) & Advanced Placement (C-AAA-AP).
  - 6th Senate, 10/23/1973 - 11/26/1973 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    C-AAA subcommittee on Evaluation of Teaching (C-AAA-ET) minutes & reports (part 1).
  - 6th Senate, 10/23/1973 - 11/26/1973 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    C-AAA subcommittee on Evaluation of Teaching (C-AAA-ET) minutes & reports (part 2).
  - 6th Senate, 10/17/1973 - 05/02/1974 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    C-AAA panels and subcommittee minutes: Panel on the grading system (C-AAA-PGS) / subcommittee on University and Departmental Honors (C-AAA-UDH) / Gores and Dinkelspiel Awards Selection Panel (C-AAA-GDASP); Academic calendar.
  - 6th Senate (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Committee on Committees (CoC) reports (1).
  - 6th Senate (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Committee on Committees (CoC) reports (2).
  - 6th Senate (Box 37, Folder 8)
    Committee on Committees (CoC) worksheets (1).
  - 6th Senate (Box 37, Folder 9)
    Committee on Committees (CoC) worksheets (2).
  - 6th Senate, 10/16/1973 - 03/14/1974 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - 6th Senate (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - 6th Senate, 10/30/1973 - 05/28/1974 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - 6th Senate, 10/30/1973 - 05/28/1974 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    Energy conservation; faculty self-discipline; Faculty & Staff Affairs (C-FSA).
  - 6th Senate, 27150 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    Faculty & Staff Affairs (C-FSA): bargaining unit employee strike.
  - 6th Senate, 09/20/1973 - 05/23/1974 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    Committee of Fifteen (C-15) memos; Committee on Foreign Study Programs (C-FSP) minutes.
  - 6th Senate, 09/26/1973 - 06/12/1974 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - 6th Senate (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Panel on Health & Safety (P-HS); Human Relations Commission (HRC); Panel on Human Subjects in Research (P-HSR).
  - 6th Senate (Box 38, Folder 9)
    Information officer & press relations; Committee on International Studies (C-IS).
  - 6th Senate (Box 38, Folder 10)
    Judicial (Campus Judicial Panel - CJP) miscellaneous.
  - 6th Senate, 08/24/1973 - 04/17/1974 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    Committee on Land & Building Development (C-LBD) minutes (includes minutes of the subcommittee on residential development, C-LBD-RD).
  - 6th Senate, 10/18/1973 - 06/04/1974 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Committee on Libraries (C-LIB) & University Library Council (ULC) minutes.
  - 6th Senate (Box 39, Folder 2)
    Meeting schedules; Memberships & Privileges (C-MP); Minority Affairs.
  - 6th Senate (Box 39, Folder 3)
    Placement services; Panel on Protection of Privacy of Information (P-PPI).
  - 6th Senate (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Committee on the Professoriate at Stanford (C-PS) & Floor Management Committee on the Professoriate at Stanford (FMC-PS) reports, drafts, memos.
  - 6th Senate, 10/11/1973 - 02/20/1974 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    Committee on Public Events (C-PEV) minutes (includes minutes of the subcommittee on University Lectures, C-PEV-UL); Panel on Radiological Hazards (P-RH); relations with student government.
  - 6th Senate, 11/02/1973 - 05/07/1974 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - 6th Senate (Box 39, Folder 7)
    Residences / student: report on Escondido Village.
  - 6th Senate (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - 6th Senate (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - 7th Senate (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 7th Senate, 05/09/1974 - 11/21/1974 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - 7th Senate, 12/12/1974 - 03/06/1975 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - 7th Senate, 04/03/1975 - 06/12/1975 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - 7th Senate, 05/16/1974 - 10/30/1974 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - 7th Senate, 11/13/1974 - 03/26/1975 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - 7th Senate, 04/03/1975 - 05/21/1975 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - 7th Senate (Box 40, Folder 8)
    Steering Committee (StC) documents #2021 - #2066.
  - 7th Senate (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Steering Committee (StC) documents #2098 - #2177.
  - 7th Senate (Box 40, Folder 9)
    Steering Committee (StC) documents #2067 - #2095.
  - 7th Senate, 1974 - 1975 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement (C-AAA) and all subcommittees minutes (1). [Note: folders organized by Academic Secretary's Office in reverse chronological order.]
  - 7th Senate, 1974 - 1975 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement (C-AAA) and all subcommittees minutes (2). [Note: folders organized by Academic Secretary's Office in reverse chronological order.]
  - 7th Senate, 1974 - 1975 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement (C-AAA) and all subcommittees minutes (3). [Note: folders organized by Academic Secretary's Office in reverse chronological order.]
  - 7th Senate, 10/31/1974 - 02/05/1975 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    Academic calendar; Academic Council membership; academic freedom; Advisory Board; affirmative action; ASSU; Committee on Athletics, Physical Education, & Recreation (C-APER) minutes.
  - 7th Senate (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - 7th Senate, 10/22/1974 - 04/16/1975 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    Computation Facilities (C-CF); Committee on the Education and Employment of Women in the University (C-EEWU) minutes; faculty self-discipline; Faculty & Staff Affairs (C-FSA); Committee of Fifteen (C-15) documents.
  - 7th Senate, 02/14/1974 - 03/18/1975 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - 7th Senate, 09/25/1974 - 04/02/1975 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    Committee on Graduate Studies (C-GS) degree lists, reports, and minutes. [Note: folders organized by the Academic Secretary's Office in reverse chronological order.]
  - 7th Senate (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Graduate Special - Ph.D.
  - 7th Senate (Box 42, Folder 2)
    Grievance procedures; information officer; International Studies - Advisory Committee; investment responsibility; Judicial Panel (CJP).
  - 7th Senate, 10/03/1974 - 05/15/1975 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Committee on Land & Building Development (C-LBD) minutes (includes subcommittee on parking & transportation. [Note: folders organized by the Academic Secretary's Office in reverse chronological order.]
  - 7th Senate, 10/17/1974 - 05/30/1975 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    Committee on Libraries (C-LIB) minutes and reports; Library Council minutes. Part 1. [Note: folders organized by the Academic Secretary's Office in reverse chronological order.]
  - 7th Senate, 10/17/1974 - 05/30/1975 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    Committee on Libraries (C-LIB) minutes and reports; Library Council minutes. Part 2. [Note: folders organized by the Academic Secretary's Office in reverse chronological order.]
  - 7th Senate (Box 42, Folder 6)
    Long range financial forecast; meeting schedule.
  - 7th Senate, 05/23/1974 - 05/15/1975 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    Professoriate: policy statements, resolutions, reports (Part 1).
  - 7th Senate, 05/23/1974 - 05/15/1975 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    Professoriate: policy statements, resolutions, reports (Part 2).
  - 7th Senate, 11/06/1973 - 04/17/1975 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    Committee on Public Events (C-PEV) minutes (includes subcommittee on University Lectures - C-PEV-U-LECT).
  - 7th Senate (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - 7th Senate, 10/08/1974 - 11/19/1974 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - 7th Senate (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Student members of committees: rosters, memos, miscellaneous documents.
  - 7th Senate, 10/22/1974 - 05/14/1975 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    Committee on Undergraduate Admissions & Financial Aids (C-UAFA): reports, documents, and minutes. [Note: folders organized by the Academic Secretary's Office in reverse chronological order.]
  - 7th Senate, 06/04/1974 - 05/21/1975 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    Committee on Undergraduate Studies (C-US): reports, documents, and minutes (Part 1). [Note: folders organized by the Academic Secretary's Office in reverse chronological order.]
  - 7th Senate, 06/04/1974 - 05/21/1975 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    Committee on Undergraduate Studies (C-US): reports, documents, and minutes (Part 2). [Note: folders organized by the Academic Secretary's Office in reverse chronological order.]
  - 7th Senate, 10/15/1974 - 06/10/1975 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    Administrative Panel on the University Press (AP-UP) minutes.
- Committee records, 1904-1986; Series 2
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Boxes 19-23 are restricted.
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Admission to Academic Council, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic Council By-Laws (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Athletics (men), 1916-1924 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Athletics (men), 1924-1930 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Athletics (men), 1930-1942 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Subcommittee on Recreational Programs and Facilities, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Subcommittee on Recreational Programs and Facilities, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Subcommittee on Recreational Programs and Facilities, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Committees Preliminary Report, 1959 Apr 13 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Committees, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee, 1909-1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee (misc.) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee (misc.) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee (misc.) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee on Limitation of Men (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Athletic Committee, 1961-1965 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Committee on Organization (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Committee on Organization, 1904 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Study Programs, Committee on: Subcommittee on Special (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Studies Program Committee Minutes, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Studies Program Committee Minutes, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Studies Program Committee Minutes, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Studies Programs Committee Minutes, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Studies Programs Committee Minutes, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Studies Programs Committee Minutes, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Studies Programs Committee Minutes, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Studies Programs, Committee on- Minutes (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Studies Program-Austria (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Studies Program-Britain, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Studies Program-Britain, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Studies Program-France (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Studies Program-Germany (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Studies Program- Italy (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - General (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Graduation (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Graduate Division, 1961-1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Graduate Division, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Graduate Division, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Graduate Division, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Graduate Division, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Graduate Study (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Graduate Study, 1953-1961 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Independent Study Committee, 1925-1928 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Independent Study Committee, 1928-1931 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Independent Study Committee, 1928-1944 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Independent Study Committee, 1932-1933 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Independent Study Committee, 1933-1935 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Independent Study Committee, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Independent Study Committee, 1935-1937 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Independent Study Plan Committee, 1937-1943 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Library Committee (notebook), 1900-1913 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Library Committee (misc.) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Library Committee, 1906-1910 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Library Committee, 1910-1916 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Library Committee, 1929-1971 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Library Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Lower Division Committee (misc.) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Lower Division Committee, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 8)